Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - T-Z
        - T-Connection - Totally connected, 1979; SR-27996; T-Connection (Box 73)
          Catalog # 30014; A-side Matrix # DA 30014 A Am
          Dash
          Hialeah, Florida
        - T-Connection - Party night; The best of my love, 1982; SR-27997; T-Connection (Box 73)
          Catalog # SPRO-9760/61; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9760-97953 G-1 A V LEMAY
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - T-Connection - T-Connection, 1978; SR-27998; T-Connection (Box 73)
          Catalog # 30009; A-side Matrix # DASH 30009 Am A
        - T-Connection - T-Connection, 1978; SR-27999; T-Connection (Box 73)
        - T-Motion & Group - T-Motion & Group, 1981; SR-29000; T-Motion & Group (Box 73)
          Catalog # AVI-40008; A-side Matrix # 021-4000X8A PV HW/WSS
          AVI Records
        - Ta Mara & The Seen - Ta Mara & The Seen, 1985; SR-29001; Ta Mara & The Seen (Box 73)
          Catalog # SP-6-5078; A-side Matrix # A 2 A SPO65078-A RCA 1
          A&M Records
        - Ta Mara & The Seen - Blueberry gossip, 1988; SR-29002; Ta Mara & The Seen (Box 73)
          Catalog # SP-5153; A-side Matrix # 1 SP-05153-A ES-1 EMW
        - Tabou Combo De Petion Ville - 8th Sacrement, 1974; SR-29003; Tabou Combo De Petion Ville (Box 73)
          Catalog # SPLP-8005; A-side Matrix # SPLP-8005-A 1A 2HK
          Unidisc
          Montreal, Quebec
        - Tabou Combo Superstars - Tabou Combo Superstars, 1978; SR-29004; Tabou Combo Superstars (Box 73)
          Catalog # MRS 1070; A-side Matrix # MRS 1070-A MA
          Mini Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Tabou Combo - L'an 10, 1977; SR-29005; Tabou Combo (Box 73)
          Catalog # RR 3377; A-side Matrix # ROTEL 3377 B-04
          Rotel Records
          Flushing, New York
        - Tabou Combo - Allo allo (toujou, Souça), 1984; SR-29006; Tabou Combo (Box 73)
          Catalog # CR-LP 8035; A-side Matrix # CRLP-8035-A
          Tabou Combo Records And Tapes
          Haiti
        - Tackhead - Strange things, 1990; SR-29007; Tackhead (Box 73)
          Catalog # SBK LP 1003; A-side Matrix # SBKLP 1003 A-1 J-1-1
          SBK Records
          England
        - Tairrie B. - The power of a woman, 1990; SR-29008; Tairrie B. (Box 73)
          Catalog # MCA-6409; A-side Matrix # MCA 9860 BG2
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Talk Talk - Talk Talk, 1982; SR-29009; Talk Talk (Box 73)
          Catalog # 12EMI 5284; A-side Matrix # 12 EMI 5284 A-1 NICK2 PENTHOUSE MASTERING ABBEYROAD
          EMI
          United Kingdom
        - Talking Heads - Fear of music, 1979; SR-29010; Talking Heads (Box 73)
          Catalog # SRK 6076; A-side Matrix # SRK 1 6076-LW1
          Sire
          New York, New York
        - Talking Heads - Remain in light, 1980; SR-29011; Talking Heads (Box 73)
          Catalog # SRK 6095; A-side Matrix # SRK 1 6095-LJW #4
        - Talking Heads - Little creatures, 1985; SR-29012; Talking Heads (Box 73)
          Catalog # 1-25305; A-side Matrix # SPO-15M1 1 SLM 9715 SH-SP B-21284 SH1 1-25305-A SH1
        - Talking Heads - Stop making sense, 1984; SR-29013; Talking Heads (Box 73)
          Catalog # 1-25186; A-side Matrix # 1-25186-A A SH1 B-19701-SH1 SLM 7401 1-1
        - Tambu - The cry, 1990; SR-29014; Tambu (Box 73)
          Catalog # CR 011; A-side Matrix # CR-010-A VP-CS TAMBU 90
          Charlie's Records
        - Tanker, Andre - BIM, 1975; SR-29015; Tanker, Andre (Box 73)
          Catalog # BIM; A-side Matrix # BIM-1-A
          Sharc
          Trinidad and Tobago
        - Tantra - The double album (disc one), 1980; SR-29016; Tantra (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29017. Double album.
          Catalog # MP-310-1; A-side Matrix # MP-310-1 JS/MW Hi FRANK N-47
          Importe/12
        - Tantra - The double album (disc two), 1980; SR-29017; Tantra (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29016. Double album.
          Catalog # MP-310-1; A-side Matrix # MP-310-3 js/MW N-47 Hi LAURIE
        - Tashan - On the horizon, 1989; SR-29018; Tashan (Box 73)
          Catalog # 465521 1; A-side Matrix # 465 521-1 A1
          CBS
          London, United Kingdom
        - Taste Of Honey - Another taste, 1979; SR-29019; Taste Of Honey (Box 73)
          Catalog # SOO-11951; A-side Matrix # SOO-1-11951-Z-3 TML-S
        - Tavares - Never had a love like this before, 1978; SR-29020; Tavares (Box 73)
          Catalog # S-95388; A-side Matrix # S-95388-B F-2 Wavy
        - Tavares, Victor - Come into the heartbeat; First house on the right side, 1981; SR-29021; Tavares, Victor (Box 73)
          Catalog # PRO 151; A-side Matrix # PRO-151-81NP5487-PW (PR)
          Polydor
        - Taylor, Gary - G.T., 1983; SR-29022; Taylor, Gary (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29023. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-4976; A-side Matrix # A&M SP04976A-ES1 Emw
        - Taylor, Gary - G.T., 1983; SR-29023; Taylor, Gary (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29022. 2 copies.
        - Taylor, Johnnie - Superhits, 1982; SR-29024; Taylor, Johnnie (Box 73)
          Catalog # MPS-8520; A-side Matrix # P GH MPS 8520 A-X
          Stax
          Berkeley, California
        - Taylor, Lewis - Lewis Taylor, 1996; SR-29025; Taylor, Lewis (Box 73)
          Catalog # ILPS 8049; A-side Matrix # ILPS 8049 A2
          Island Records
        - Teardrop Explodes - Wilder, 1981; SR-29026; Teardrop Explodes (Box 73)
          Catalog # SRM-1-4035; A-side Matrix # HW SRM-1-4035-AS-PRC-C-1-1-1
          Mercury
        - Tears For Fears - Songs from the big chair, 1985; SR-29027; Tears For Fears (Box 73)
          Catalog # 422-824 300-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # H 422824300-1-AS-PRC-R 3-2-3-Q
        - Tease - Remember…., 1988; SR-29028; Tease (Box 73)
          Catalog # E 40376; A-side Matrix # A 3 AL-40376-ADMM G1
          Epic
          Los Angeles, California
        - Tease - Better wild (than mild), 1986; SR-29029; Tease (Box 73)
          Catalog # 49-05932; A-side Matrix # P (P) XSS-173743-1B
        - Tease - Tease, 1983; SR-29030; Tease (Box 73)
          Catalog # AFL1-4597; A-side Matrix # A1 B AFL1-4597-A-105
          RCA
        - Techfunkers - Rock da techfunk (1996 remix), 1996; SR-29031; Techfunkers (Box 73)
          Catalog # SEX-017; A-side Matrix # CSP SEX-017-A muns
          Sex Mania
        - Teen Dream - Let's get busy, 1987; SR-29032; Teen Dream (Box 73)
          Catalog # 1-25493; A-side Matrix # 1-25493-A-SR1 1-1
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - Teena Marie - It must be magic, 1981; SR-29033; Teena Marie (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29034. Different discs.
          Catalog # G8-1004M1; A-side Matrix # G 81004 M1-A-15A zva#13 JGS BBX
          Gordy
        - Teena Marie - Square biz, 1981; SR-29034; Teena Marie (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29033. Different discs.
          Catalog # M 35000V1; A-side Matrix # M-35000 V1 A 66349 D RE1 -15C zur#13 BET JGS
          Motown
        - Telex - Neurovision, 1980; SR-29035; Telex (Box 73)
          Catalog # SRK 6090; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-6090-LW1
        - Nino Tempo & 5th Ave. Sax - Come see me 'round midnight, 1974; SR-29036; Nino Tempo & 5th Ave. Sax (Box 73)
          Catalog # SP-3629; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 3660 (RE-1)-P1
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Temprees - Lovemen, 1972; SR-29037; Temprees (Box 73)
          Catalog # XPS-1901; A-side Matrix # STXS-0231-6 XS-0 375 L NIX SON K-5484
          We Produce Records
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Temptations - 25th Anniversary (disc one), 1986; SR-29038; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29039. Double album.
          Catalog # 5389ML2; A-side Matrix # 5389ML2-A-1SA m zcx #12
        - Temptations - 25th Anniversary (disc two), 1986; SR-29039; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29038. Double album.
          Catalog # 5389ML2; A-side Matrix # 5389ML3-1SB ZC m Z/2 DOMINIC-CU DENVER
        - Temptations - The temptin' temptations, 1965; SR-29040; Temptations (Box 73)
          Catalog # G-914; A-side Matrix # H-1330 R SR4M--2641-1-D A
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Temptations - Wings of love, 1976; SR-29041; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29042. 2 copies.
          Catalog # G6-971S1; A-side Matrix # SUPERIOR G6-97151-2541-S-RE1-06C 20416
        - Temptations - Wings of love, 1976; SR-29042; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29041. 2 copies.
        - Temptations - Anthology (disc one), 1973; SR-29043; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29044. Triple album.
          Catalog # M 782A3; A-side Matrix # JL A 3 M-782-2A C4R5-7865-13A PPN
        - Temptations - Anthology (disc three), 1973; SR-29044; Temptations (Box 73)
          In same jacket as # SR-29043. Triple album.
          Catalog # M 782A3; A-side Matrix # JL A M-782-A 3 C4R5-7869-13A PPN
        - Tender Spot - Rock on, 1982; SR-29045; Tender Spot; Stevens, Carey (Box 74)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # JW-92381-A VIRTUE CS PO11CA PA SMR
          B's Records
        - Terence FM - Feelin' kinda high, 2002; SR-29046; Terence FM (Box 74)
          Catalog # CAJ 281; A-side Matrix # PCMJR-HEMI CAJ-281-A
          Cajual Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Teresa - Class reunion, 1979; SR-29047; Teresa (Box 74)
          Catalog # DA 3502; A-side Matrix # A1 E DA-3502-A-1
          Dream Records
        - Termini Project, Richard - Dangerous games, 1983; SR-29048; Termini Project, Richard (Box 74)
          Catalog # RT804; A-side Matrix # RT-804-A-RE1 S1
          Dyslexia
        - Terry Project, Todd - To the batmobile let's go, 1988; SR-29049; Terry Project, Todd (Box 74)
          Catalog # LPRE-82009X; A-side Matrix # LPRE-82009X ''Todd To The Batmobile, Let's Go!!'' cg
          Fresh Records
        - Tex, Joe - He who is without funk cast the first stone, 1978; SR-29050; Tex, Joe (Box 74)
          Catalog # 6100; A-side Matrix # ASY15Z914-1E
          Dial
        - Thara Humara - Introspection (special D.J. remixes), 1991; SR-29051; Thara Humara (Box 74)
          Catalog # BASIX-031; A-side Matrix # BASIX-03 1 A + II 1
          Basic Mix
          Barcelona, Spain
        - Theodore, Mike - Hellfire, 1984; SR-29052; Theodore, Mike (Box 74)
          Catalog # ET-1203; A-side Matrix # A-1 ET 1203 A F/W Ȼ
          Earthtone Recording Company
        - Theresa - Broken puzzle, 1987; SR-29053; Theresa (Box 74)
          Catalog # 6488-1-R; A-side Matrix # 6488-1-R-A 3S emw
          RCA Victor
        - Thin Lizzy - Johnny the fox meets Jimmy the weed, 1976; SR-29054; Thin Lizzy (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29055. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SRM-1-1119; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-1119-A-9
        - Thin Lizzy - Johnny the fox meets Jimmy the weed, 1976; SR-29055; Thin Lizzy (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29054. 2 copies.
        - Third World - Talk to me, 1979; SR-29056; Third World (Box 74)
          Catalog # ISD 8846; A-side Matrix # ISD-8846-WAA-8168-VII-S-M1 24339-X 2
          Island Mercury
        - Thomas & Taylor - True love book 1, 1987; SR-29058; Thomas & Taylor (Box 74)
          Catalog # ICH 1007; A-side Matrix # ICH-1007-A DCHARLES
          Ichiban Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Thomas, Irma - Safe with me, 1980; SR-29059; Thomas, Irma (Box 74)
          Catalog # RCS-1006-D; A-side Matrix # RCS-1006-DA
          RCS Records
          Baton Rouge, Louisiana
        - Thomas, Joe - Feelin's from within, 1976; SR-29060; Thomas, Joe (Box 74)
          Catalog # GM-3315; A-side Matrix # GM-3315A-2 ae Brown FW/CS
          Groove Merchant
        - Thomas, Margot - Move it, 1979; SR-29061; Thomas, Margot (Box 74)
          Catalog # DC 7035; A-side Matrix # DC -7035-A-RE
          Deco
          United States
        - Thomas, Rufus - Chronicle: their greatest stax hits, 1979; SR-29062; Thomas, Rufus; Thomas, Carla (Box 74)
          Catalog # STX-4124; A-side Matrix # FS2279TD TMPCRPTH#2 T1 STX4124ARE1-1
        - Thomas, Rufus - Rappin' Rufus, 1985; SR-29063; Thomas, Rufus (Box 74)
          Catalog # 12-103; A-side Matrix # 1 DM 12103A DM =
        - Thomas, Sam Fan - Sam Fan Thomas, 1986; SR-29064; Thomas, Sam Fan (Box 74)
          Catalog # MS5004; A-side Matrix # I MST 5004 A1
          MST Production
          France
        - Thomas, Tammy - It's getting better, 1987; SR-29065; Thomas, Tammy (Box 74)
          Catalog # PHR-417; A-side Matrix # PHR-417 A C9
          Play House Records
        - Thomas, Timmy - Freak in, freak out, 1978; SR-29066; Thomas, Timmy (Box 74)
          Catalog # TKD-111; A-side Matrix # TKD 111 A
          T.K. Disco
        - Thomas, Timmy - Timmy Thomas live, 1979; SR-29067; Thomas, Timmy (Box 74)
          Catalog # LP-7517; A-side Matrix # GL 7517 A
          Glades
        - Thomas, Timmy - Timmy Thomas live, 1979; SR-29068; Thomas, Timmy (Box 74)
        - Thompson, Don - Fanny Brown, 1977; SR-29069; Thompson, Don (Box 74)
          Catalog # BL 754215; A-side Matrix # BMG7-5091-1A
          Brunswick
        - Thomson, Ali - Deception is an art, 1981; SR-29070; Thomson, Ali (Box 74)
          Catalog # SP-4846; A-side Matrix # AM SP 04846-A P1
        - Three Dog Night - Harmony, 1971; SR-29071; Three Dog Night (Box 74)
          Catalog # DSX-50108; A-side Matrix # 1 C1 R-100079-A-1S
          ABC/Dunhill Records
        - Three'n One - Soul freak; Drop & roll, 1997; SR-29072; Three'n One (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29073. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 510 411; A-side Matrix # 743 215 104 11-A1
          Fire Recordings
          Germany
        - Three'n One - Soul freak; Drop & roll, 1997; SR-29073; Three'n One (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29072. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 510 411; A-side Matrix # 744 215 104 11-A1
        - Thrust - Can't wait to get to you, 1982; SR-29074; Thrust (Box 74)
          Catalog # AP-115-RE1; A-side Matrix # a Jonathan Fearing ''Mystery MIX'' AP-115-A-RE1
          Apexton Records
          Long Island City, New York
        - Thurston, Bobby - Is something wrong with you, 1981; SR-29075; Thurston, Bobby (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29076. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL D 528; A-side Matrix # P RLD 528AS-1A Vang/FK CBS NYC
          Prelude Records
        - Thurston, Bobby - Is something wrong with you, 1981; SR-29076; Thurston, Bobby (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29075. 2 copies.
        - Tierra - Tierra, 1981; SR-29077; Tierra (Box 74)
          Catalog # SA 8541; A-side Matrix # SA-8541-A FWCJ
          Salsoul Records
        - Tide, High - Time unlimited, 1991; SR-29078; Tide, High (Box 74)
          Catalog # MEET 421; A-side Matrix # MEET 421 A
          Meet Records
          Italy
        - Time - Pandemonium, 1990; SR-29079; Time (Box 74)
          Catalog # 1-27490; A-side Matrix # 1-27490-A SR1 1-1
          Paisley Park
        - Time Bandits - Time Bandits, 1985; SR-29080; Time Bandits (Box 74)
          Catalog # BFC 40069; A-side Matrix # P AP AL40069-1C
          Columbia
        - Tina B - Tina B, 1984; SR-29081; Tina B (Box 74)
          Catalog # 60364-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60364-A 4 1-1
          Elektra
        - Tina B - Miracles explode, 1987; SR-29082; Tina B (Box 74)
          Catalog # CR12-019; A-side Matrix # CR12-012-A HERbIE JR
          Criminal Records
        - Titan - Corazon (disc one), 1999; SR-29083; Titan (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29084; SR-29085; SR-29086. 2 copies, Double album.
          Catalog # 7087 6 15718 1 3; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-15718-1-3 SIDE A
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - Titan - Corazon (disc one), 1999; SR-29084; Titan (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29083; SR-29085; SR-29086. 2 copies, Double album.
        - Titan - Corazon (disc two), 1999; SR-29085; Titan (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29083; SR-29084; SR-29086. 2 copies, Double album.
          Catalog # 7087 6 15718 1 3; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-15718-1-3 ores SIDE C
        - Titan - Corazon (disc two), 1999; SR-29086; Titan (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29083; SR-29084; SR-29085. 2 copies, Double album.
        - T.J.M. - Put yourself in my place; I don't need no music, 1979; SR-29087; T.J.M.; Davison, Alfie; Baker, Arthur; Wedgeworth, Larry; Carbone, Tony (Box 74)
          Catalog # NBD 20195 DJ; A-side Matrix # TM/JR NBD-20195-AS-CP2
          Casablanca
        - TKA - Scars of love, 1987; SR-29088; TKA (Box 74)
          Catalog # TBLP 1011; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1011-A HErbIE JR ''THERE WILL ALWAYS BE A YOU''
          Tommy Boy
        - TNT Orchestra - Together, 1977; SR-29089; TNT Orchestra (Box 74)
          Catalog # DIS LP 1001; A-side Matrix # DIS-LP 1001-A St
          Disco International
        - To Be Continued - Free to be, 1993; SR-29090; To Be Continued (Box 74)
          Catalog # DMD 1985; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-65085-65140-65141-1
          Eastwest Records America
        - T.O.C. - Bring the house down, 1987; SR-29091; T.O.C. (Box 74)
          Catalog # UR 929; A-side Matrix # pa a 87 UR-929-A
          Urban Rock Records
        - Tom Tom Club - Close to the bone, 1983; SR-29092; Tom Tom Club (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29093. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23916; A-side Matrix # 12 3916 A WW3
          Sire Records Company
        - Tom Tom Club - Close to the bone, 1983; SR-29093; Tom Tom Club (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29092. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23916; A-side Matrix # 13 3916 A WW3 #3
        - Tom Tom Club - Tom Tom Club, 1981; SR-29094; Tom Tom Club (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29095. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SRK 3628; A-side Matrix # gc SRK 1 3628-LW1
        - Tom Tom Club - Tom Tom Club, 1981; SR-29095; Tom Tom Club (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29094. 2 copies.
        - Tomorrow's Edition - A song for everyone, 1982; SR-29096; Tomorrow's Edition (Box 74)
          Catalog # 80009-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-824969-A 0-1 SM1-2
          Atlantic
        - Toms, Gary - Turn it out, 1977; SR-29097; Toms, Gary (Box 74)
          Catalog # MCA-2289; A-side Matrix # MCA 1291 W1
        - Tonasia - Tears of tears, 1991; SR-29098; Tonasia (Box 74)
          Catalog # MIC-559; A-side Matrix # MIC-559-A C1 G1 CA1 -pa-4-91 A6
          Micmac Records, Inc.
        - Tone-Lōc - Lōc'ed after dark, 1989; SR-29099; Tone-Lōc (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29100. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DV3000DJ; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK DMM DV-3000-A-DMM SP1-4 SP-AR
          Delicous Vinyl
        - Tone-Lōc - Lōc'ed after dark, 1989; SR-29100; Tone-Lōc (Box 74)
          In same jacket as # SR-29099. 2 copies.
        - Tone Loc - On fire; Cheeba cheeba, 1987; SR-29101; Tone Loc (Box 74)
          Catalog # DV-001; A-side Matrix # 5 18338 1-1 TRIGGER IS DOWN
          Delicious Vinyl
        - Tony B. & The Electric Warriors - So hot, 1988; SR-29102; Tony B. & The Electric Warriors (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29103. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MDN 1009; A-side Matrix # MDN 1009 A
          Modern Music Productions
          Milan, Italy
        - Tony B. & The Electric Warriors - So hot, 1988; SR-29103; Tony B. & The Electric Warriors (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29102. 2 copies.
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - The blues, 1990; SR-29104; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29105. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 873 995-1; A-side Matrix # DMS HERbIE JR 873-995-1-AS HUB
          Wing Records
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - The blues, 1990; SR-29105; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)